overcomeeverything.com 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy – Overcome Everything!

OVERCOME EVERYTHING.COM PRIVACY POLICY  
— IMPORTANT — PLEASE READ

LAST UPDATED: June 11, 2010

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the commitment to your privacy on the part of Overcome Everything, Inc. (referred to collectively as “we” and “us”).

PERSONS OR PARTIES COVERED

This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors to any Overcome Everything owned website (the “Website”), all subscribers to Overcome Everything-sponsored lists and/or newsletters (whether paid or unpaid), all members and/or affiliates sponsored by or owned by Overcome Everything (whether paid or unpaid), all affiliates of any site sponsored or owned by Overcome Everything (whether paid or unpaid), and all customers that purchase products and/or services via the Website or otherwise from Overcome Everything.  Persons who visit or view the Website, whether intentionally or unintentionally, whether solicited or unsolicited, are referred to herein as “Visitors” and are subject to this Privacy Policy. Subscribers to Overcome Everything-sponsored lists and/or newsletters are referred to herein as “Subscribers” and are subject to the Privacy Policy. Persons who join an organization or marketing endeavor (e.g. “affiliates”) promoted by and through the Website, or otherwise by Overcome Everything are referred to herein as “Members” and are subject to this Privacy Policy.  Individuals that order, attempt to order or receive products and/or services that are sold, advertised on or delivered from the Website, or otherwise by Overcome Everything, even at no cost, are referred to herein as “Customers” and are subject to this Privacy Policy.

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please contact us at www.TellmanSupport.com.  Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law.

MINORS

We do not knowingly collect information from individuals under eighteen (18) years of age, or persons who are otherwise covered by the provisions of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, as amended (“COPPA”).  No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Website by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age.  We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

VIEWING, USE AND/OR COMMUNICATION IS CONSTRUED AS ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy is a portion of the consideration required for your right to visit the Website.  If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy in their entirety, you have no right to visit the Website.

ABOUT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION OVERCOME EVERYTHING COLLECTS AND HOW IT IS USED

Overcome Everything routinely collects information about Visitors, Subscribers, Members and Customers.  This information is obtained in various ways, such as:

VISITOR, SUBSCRIBER, MEMBER OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM REGISTRATION

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Registration” means that the Visitor, Subscriber, Member or Customer, as applicable, takes active, positive steps to communicate information to Overcome Everything.  This can include, without limitation, where the individual: (a) registers for a newsletter or subscribe to a mailing list; (b) participates in Visitor surveys; (c) participates in promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes offered by Overcome Everything; (d) requests information from Overcome Everything via an online form, email, mail or courier; (e) joins, or attempts to join, an affiliate program or other membership organization sponsored by Overcome Everything; and/or (f) orders a product through the Website or otherwise from Overcome Everything.

The information that you must supply in connection with Registration (as further described below) may include, without limitation, some or all of the following: (i) your full name; (ii) company name; (iii) e-mail address; (iv) mailing address (and billing address if different); (v) home telephone number; (vi) work telephone number; (vii) telecopier number; (viii) credit card information; and/or (ix) any other information requested on the applicable Registration form.

VISITOR EMAIL INQUIRIES

Website Visitors that wish to communicate with Overcome Everything do so under the following conditions: (a) they give their permission to be contacted by Overcome Everything; and (b) they are subject to any ‘submission’ provisions contained in the Overcome Everything Terms of Use, Overcome Everything Purchase Agreement and/or this Privacy Policy.  The email address that you use in connection with your inquiry shall be added to the Overcome Everything database.

CUSTOMER EMAIL OR TESTIMONIALS

If you are a Customer and you send an email to Overcome Everything, or if you communicate with Overcome Everything by phone or U.S. mail, Overcome Everything shall collect information about your communication and by communicating with Overcome Everything, you give your permission for Overcome Everything to collect, archive, retrieve and otherwise use any information collected as Overcome Everything sees fit.

Any communication which, in its sole discretion, Overcome Everything deems to be a testimonial, may be publicized for commercial purposes.

INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM VOLUNTARY VISITOR, SUBSCRIBER, MEMBER OR CUSTOMER  
SURVEYS

Unless otherwise specified in the survey, you must assume that any information provided to Overcome Everything as part of a survey in which you participate may be used as set forth herein below.

INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ELECTRONIC MEANS AND COOKIES

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the sections of the Website.  This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g. America Online, Earthlink). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Website and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Website usage, as well as to offer you products and services. We also reserve the right to use aggregate or group data about our Visitors for any and all lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or characteristics of our visitors as a group. By visiting and/or supplying your personal information at the Website, you agree to allow us to provide such aggregate data to third parties.

“Cookies” is web jargon for bits of computer code placed on your hard drive.  The Website uses cookies to keep you ‘logged in,’ to keep track of search criteria, to monitor use, to password protect use of the Website and/or to track use of products and/or services sold by and through the Website.  Even in the case where a Visitor rejects a cookie, they may still use our Website.  The only drawback to this is that the Visitor may be limited in what he/she can access in some areas on our Website.  Cookies can also be used to obtain information about your computer configuration or your use of your computer.  To find out more about cookies, including how to disable and/or remove cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com.

HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

The personal information that you submit to us remains your property, but by submitting such information to us you grant us the right, subject to applicable state and federal law, to use the personal information (other than credit card information) for marketing purposes.  Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute any and all personal information with/to any third-party for any and all uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law. These third parties may include, but shall not be limited to: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers; (c) telemarketers (where permitted by applicable law); (d) SMS text-based marketers (where permitted by applicable law); and (e) direct marketers.  We may also use your personal information for any promotion-related purpose, and/or marketing and survey purpose, on our own behalf and on behalf of our affiliates and subsidiaries. We may disclose personal information to third-party agents and independent contractors that help us create and/or operate any promotions, surveys or other offerings. You agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Website and any and all offerings made available therein, or otherwise by Overcome Everything.

We are able to offer our products and services to you, in part, based on your willingness to be reached by our third-party advertisers.  Your personal information (other than credit card information) will be shared with advertisers on an aggregate and non-aggregate basis.  We also use contact information from your personal information to send you information about us, our products and services and to contact you about your billing account status.   Please keep in mind, though, that we do not control, and are not responsible for, the practices of our third-party advertisers.  If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us and/or third party advertisers, or if you wish to prevent the transfer and/or sale of your personal information to third parties (subject to restrictions contained in applicable state and federal law), please see the Opt-Out/Unsubscribe section below.

You agree that by submitting your personal information to Overcome Everything, you agree to receive e-mail marketing from Overcome Everything and our third-party advertisers.  In addition, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq. (the “ATSR”). With respect to the ATSR, and notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the terms of the ATSR.

In addition, by submitting your personal information to Overcome Everything, you agree to receive mobile marketing including, but not limited to, text-message based marketing, from us and our third party advertisers and marketers (where, and to the extent that, such marketing is permitted by applicable law).  As such, notwithstanding that your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal Do-Not-Call registries, we retain the right to contact you via text-message based marketing in accordance with applicable state and federal law.  Further, you agree that we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute your mobile telephone and other mobile data with/to any third-party for any and all non-marketing uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

We reserve the right to release current or past personal information: (a) in the event that we believe that the Website, and any products, services or other offerings is/are being or has/have been used in violation of this Privacy Policy, the Overcome Everything Terms of Use, Overcome Everything Purchase Agreement, or to commit unlawful acts; (b) if the information is subpoenaed; or (c) if any entity comprising Overcome Everything is sold or acquired.  Moreover, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time. Visitors should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personally identifiable information to be shared or transferred to third parties without permission.

We may also supplement the information we collect with information from other sources to assist us in evaluating and improving the Website, our products and/or services, and to determine your preferences so that we can tailor the Website and our products and/or services to your needs.

CREDIT CARD INFORMATION

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not use your credit card information for any marketing purposes, or transfer same to any third party, other than as set forth in this paragraph.   Overcome Everything may: (a) transfer your credit card information to third party sellers where necessary to effectuate the purchase of products and/or services that you requested on the Website or otherwise from Overcome Everything; (b) disclose your credit card information pursuant to a court order, litigation and/or fraud investigation; and (c) share with third parties the fact that we have credit card information on file for specific individuals.

INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM VISITOR INTERACTION WITH BANNERS, POPUPS OR WEBSITE ADVERTISERS

The Website may contain third party provided banners, pop-ups, hyperlinked advertising and links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites. Overcome Everything is not responsible for the privacy practices associated with such third party advertisers and/or websites.  In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction via such advertisers and/or at such websites. These third-party websites and advertisers have separate privacy and data collection practices and Overcome Everything has no responsibility or liability relating to them.  We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such advertisers and/or websites.  These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us.

OPT-OUT/UNSUBSCRIBE

When you submit personally identifiable information to us at the Website, you have opted-in to the sharing of your personal information with third parties to receive marketing communications.  When contacted by any of these companies or third parties, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding their use and sharing of your information.  To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties, please contact us at www.TellmanSupport.com.  To stop receiving future e-mail communications from Overcome Everything, please contact us at www.TellmanSupport.com.  Overcome Everything may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes.  If e-mail recipients wish to end their e-mail subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to unsubscribe from the particular list.  To unsubscribe from all Overcome Everything e-mail lists, please contact us at www.TellmanSupport.com.

DATA SECURITY

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment.  When our registration/application process asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), and when we store and transmit such sensitive information, it is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software.  While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect sensitive information and other personal information off-line.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet, or otherwise, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we strive to protect your sensitive information and other personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this personal information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.  All of our users’ personal information, not just sensitive information, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information.  Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all Overcome Everything user personal information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action.  In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information.  You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach.  Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at:

www.TellmanSupport.com  
ListBuilding.com  
139 Main Street Suite 606E  
Brattleboro, Vermont 05301

USA

REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WITHOUT NOTICE

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time.  All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check the Website periodically for any changes.  Your continued use of the Website and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.
